const quizContent = {
    en: [
      { question: "1. How many rounds are there in a SUDO match?", options: ["1", "2", "3", "4"], answer: "3" },
      { question: "2. What is the name of the SUDO fighter's outfit?", options: ["Kimono", "Sudo clothing", "Gi", "Oda"], answer: "Oda" },
      { question: "3. What does SUDO mean in translation?", options: ["A fighting style based on hard strikes and static positions", "Combat similar to the properties of water", "An ancient martial philosophy originating in Greece"], answer: "Combat similar to the properties of water" },
      { question: "4. Who is the founder of SUDO?", options: ["Bruce Lee", "Chuck Norris", "Sabir Suleyman", "Jigoro Kano"], answer: "Sabir Suleyman" },
      { question: "5. In which year was SUDO born?", options: ["1877", "1977", "2014", "2011"], answer: "2011" },
      { question: "6. In which country was SUDO born?", options: ["Azerbaijan", "Germany", "Japan", "USA"], answer: "Azerbaijan" },
      { question: "7. Where is the SUDO headquarters located?", options: ["Dubai", "Paderborn", "Baku", "New York"], answer: "Paderborn" },
      { question: "8. Who is the Honorary President of the World SUDO Federation?", options: ["Naruhito", "Barack Hussein Obama II", "Chuck Norris"], answer: "Chuck Norris" },
      { question: "9. Who is the President of the World SUDO Federation?", options: ["Sabir Suleyman", "Antonio Bagueras", "Grandmaster Rahim", "Gary Stve"], answer: "Sabir Suleyman" },
      { question: "10. What is the core philosophy of SUDO?", options: ["Air", "Stone", "Water", "Person"], answer: "Water" },
      { question: "11. What is the SUDO greeting?", options: ["Bonjour", "Sa", "Os", "Ossu"], answer: "Sa" },
      { question: "12. What is the name of the SUDO training place?", options: ["Sudo Room", "Dodze", "Training Room", "Ojag"], answer: "Ojag" },
      { question: "13. List all rounds in a SUDO competition in order.", options: ["Mix, Doyush-Doshek, Doyush, Doshek", "Doyush, Doshek, Mix", "Doshek, Doyush, Mix"], answer: "Doyush, Doshek, Mix" },
      { question: "14. What are the uniform colors for a SUDO fighter?", options: ["White, Blue", "White, Blue, Red", "White, Red", "Red, Blue"], answer: "Red, Blue" },
      { question: "15. Which SUDO World Championship took place in Paderborn (Germany) in 2024?", options: ["8", "12", "13", "14"], answer: "13" },
      { question: "16. In how many languages was the book 'Genius SUDO' published in 2022?", options: ["1", "3", "5", "6"], answer: "6" },
      { question: "17. Which organization officially represents SUDO worldwide?", options: ["World Sudo Federation", "World SUDO Center", "Paderborn Sudo Academy", "Westfalen SUDO Association"], answer: "World Sudo Federation" },
      { question: "18. How is SUDO different from Karate, Judo and Taekwondo?", options: ["SUDO is more versatile as it combines punches, kicks, throws and ground fighting.", "SUDO is less versatile because it contains only simple punches and no ground fighting.", "SUDO focuses solely on meditation and contains no fighting techniques.", "Compared to Taekwondo, SUDO is very limited and allows no kicks or throws."], answer: "SUDO is more versatile as it combines punches, kicks, throws and ground fighting." },
      { question: "19. Why is SUDO called a universal combat system?", options: ["Because it unites striking, kicking, throwing, and ground techniques in one system.", "Because it is based only on breathing techniques and meditation.", "Because it is not meant for competition and is only for relaxation.", "Because it contains only slow movements without real techniques."], answer: "Because it unites striking, kicking, throwing, and ground techniques in one system." },
      { question: "20. What position does a SUDO fight begin in?", options: ["Dur", "Hazir", "Hazir-ol", "Atli"], answer: "Hazir-ol" }
      ,
      { question: "21. Which strikes are forbidden in SUDO (name the top 3)?", options: ["Punches to the face, strikes to the back of the head, strikes to the genitals.", "Palm strikes to the stomach, light leg taps, slaps to the cheek.", "Light foot taps, shoulder punches, knee to thigh."], answer: "Punches to the face, strikes to the back of the head, strikes to the genitals." },
      { question: "22. What stance is considered the most effective in SUDO?", options: ["Otur", "Rahat-otur", "Rahat", "Hazir-ol"], answer: "Hazir-ol" },
      { question: "23. Which combination is not effective in SUDO?", options: ["Body kick", "Three punches to the shoulder then retreat", "Foot sweep", "Ground control"], answer: "Three punches to the shoulder then retreat" },
      { question: "24. What does 'groundwork' mean in SUDO?", options: ["Doing pushups as warm-up", "Touching the opponent for victory", "Meditation phase without contact", "Second round where fighters kneel and grapple"], answer: "Second round where fighters kneel and grapple" },
      { question: "25. What action is forbidden in SUDO throws?", options: ["Throwing with a straight back", "Deliberately throwing the opponent on the head", "Breathing during the throw", "Shouting during the throw"], answer: "Deliberately throwing the opponent on the head" },
      { question: "26. What role does breathing play in a SUDO match?", options: ["Breathing is unimportant and ignored", "Only mouth breathing is allowed", "Breathing helps maintain calm and control"], answer: "Breathing helps maintain calm and control" },
      { question: "27. How is the winner of a SUDO match determined?", options: ["By points, opponent submission or technical victory", "Loudest kiai wins", "All matches end in draw"], answer: "By points, opponent submission or technical victory" },
      { question: "28. What does the term 'iki' mean in SUDO?", options: ["Groundwork", "Surrender", "Point", "Kiai"], answer: "Point" },
      { question: "29. What types of warnings exist in SUDO?", options: ["1 (Kobud)", "2 (Kobud, Jaza)", "3 (Kobud, Jaza, Chikh)", "4 (Kobud, Jaza, Chikh, Galkh)"], answer: "3 (Kobud, Jaza, Chikh)" },
      { question: "30. Which judge gesture indicates disqualification?", options: ["Kobud", "Jaza", "Chikh", "Galkh"], answer: "Chikh" },
      { question: "31. What action leads to instant disqualification in SUDO?", options: ["Deliberate punch to the head", "Too quiet kiai", "Sweat on the mat", "Intentional head strike"], answer: "Deliberate punch to the head" },
      { question: "32. Which rule does not apply to athlete equipment?", options: ["Wearing Oda is mandatory", "Sock color must match belt", "Fighters must be barefoot", "Gloves off in second round"], answer: "Sock color must match belt" },
      { question: "33. Where was the first official SUDO World Championship held?", options: ["Istanbul-2012", "Vagos-2012", "Baku-2012", "Paderborn-2012"], answer: "Baku-2012" },
      { question: "34. Which countries have the most SUDO Grandchampions?", options: ["Latvia", "Guinea-Bissau", "Azerbaijan", "Canada", "Germany", "Senegal"], answer: "Latvia" },
      { question: "35. What does the phrase 'Be like water' mean in SUDO philosophy?", options: ["Water is stronger than fire so avoid heat", "Adaptable, flowing, and strong—flexible in battle", "Fight only in the rain"], answer: "Adaptable, flowing, and strong—flexible in battle" },
      { question: "36. What does 'Otur' mean in SUDO?", options: ["Stand up", "Ready to fight", "Sit down", "Combat stance"], answer: "Sit down" },
      { question: "37. What is the highest competition score in SUDO?", options: ["Uch", "Galaba", "Bir", "Iki"], answer: "Galaba" },
      { question: "38. Student-Teacher ranking in SUDO", options: ["Bash Ustad, Namized, Ustad, Shagird, Muellim, Bash Muellim", "Namized, Ustad, Shagird, Muellim, Bash Muellim, Bash Ustad", "Namized, Shagird, Muellim, Bash Muellim, Ustad, Bash Ustad", "Shagird, Namized, Muellim, Bash Muellim, Ustad, Bash Ustad"], answer: "Shagird, Namized, Muellim, Bash Muellim, Ustad, Bash Ustad" },
      { question: "39. In 2025, the world's largest SUDO school is?", options: ["WSA Paderborn", "Baku Sudo Academy", "SUDO GmbH", "SUDO India"], answer: "WSA Paderborn" },
      { question: "40. What is SUDO's biggest goal?", options: ["Successfully hosting the next world championship", "Participating in the Olympic Games", "Opening its own world center", "Maximizing student numbers at the WSF Institute"], answer: "Participating in the Olympic Games" }
    ],
    de: [
      { question: "1. Wie viele Runden hat ein SUDO-Match?", options: ["1", "2", "3", "4"], answer: "3" },
      { question: "2. Wie heißt das Outfit des SUDO-Kämpfers?", options: ["Kimono", "Sudo Kleidung", "Gi", "Oda"], answer: "Oda" },
      { question: "3. Was bedeutet SUDO in der Übersetzung?", options: ["Ein Kampfstil, der auf harten Schlägen und statischen Positionen basiert", "Kampf ähnlich den Eigenschaften des Wassers", "Eine alte Kampfkunstphilosophie, die im antiken Griechenland entstanden ist"], answer: "Kampf ähnlich den Eigenschaften des Wassers" },
      { question: "4. Gründer von SUDO?", options: ["Bruce Lee", "Chuck Norris", "Sabir Suleyman", "Jigoro Kano"], answer: "Sabir Suleyman" },
      { question: "5. In welchem Jahr wurde SUDO gegründet?", options: ["1877", "1977", "2014", "2011"], answer: "2011" },
      { question: "6. In welchem Land wurde SUDO geboren?", options: ["Aserbaidschan", "Deutschland", "Japan", "USA"], answer: "Aserbaidschan" },
      { question: "7. Wo befindet sich der Hauptsitz von SUDO?", options: ["Dubai", "Paderborn", "Baku", "New York"], answer: "Paderborn" },
      { question: "8. Wer ist Ehrenpräsident der World SUDO Federation?", options: ["Naruhito", "Barack Hussein Obama II", "Chuck Norris"], answer: "Chuck Norris" },
      { question: "9. Wer ist Präsident der World SUDO Federation?", options: ["Sabir Suleyman", "Antonio Bagueras", "Grandmaster Rahim", "Gary Stve"], answer: "Sabir Suleyman" },
      { question: "10. Was ist die Grundphilosophie von SUDO?", options: ["Luft", "Stein", "Wasser", "Person"], answer: "Wasser" },
      { question: "11. Wie lautet der Gruß bei SUDO?", options: ["Bonjour", "Sa", "Os", "Ossu"], answer: "Sa" },
      { question: "12. Wie heißt der Ort, an dem SUDO trainiert wird?", options: ["Sudo Raum", "Dodze", "Trainingsraum", "Ojag"], answer: "Ojag" },
      { question: "13. Nennen Sie alle Runden bei einem SUDO-Wettkampf der Reihe nach.", options: ["Mix, Doyush-Doshek, Doyush, Doshek", "Doyush, Doshek, Mix", "Doshek, Doyush, Mix"], answer: "Doyush, Doshek, Mix" },
      { question: "14. Welche Farben hat die Kleidung eines SUDO-Kämpfers?", options: ["Weiß, Blau", "Weiß, Blau, Rot", "Weiß, Rot", "Rot, Blau"], answer: "Rot, Blau" },
      { question: "15. Welche SUDO-Weltmeisterschaft fand 2024 in Paderborn statt?", options: ["8", "12", "13", "14"], answer: "13" },
      { question: "16. In wie vielen Sprachen wurde das Buch 'Genius SUDO' im Jahr 2022 veröffentlicht?", options: ["1", "3", "5", "6"], answer: "6" },
      { question: "17. Welche Organisation vertritt SUDO offiziell weltweit?", options: ["World Sudo Federation", "World SUDO Center", "Paderborn Sudo Akademie", "Westfalen SUDO Association"], answer: "World Sudo Federation" },
      { question: "18. Wie unterscheidet sich SUDO von Karate, Judo und Taekwondo?", options: ["SUDO ist vielseitiger, da es Schläge, Tritte, Würfe und Bodenkampf vereint.", "SUDO ist weniger vielseitig, weil es nur einfache Schläge enthält und keinen Bodenkampf erlaubt.", "SUDO konzentriert sich ausschließlich auf Meditation und enthält keine Kampftechniken.", "Im Vergleich zu Taekwondo ist SUDO sehr eingeschränkt und erlaubt keine Tritte oder Würfe."], answer: "SUDO ist vielseitiger, da es Schläge, Tritte, Würfe und Bodenkampf vereint." },
      { question: "19. Warum wird SUDO als universelles Kampfsystem bezeichnet?", options: ["Weil es Schlagtechniken, Tritte, Würfe und Bodenkampf in einem System vereint.", "Weil es nur auf Atemtechniken und Meditation basiert.", "Weil es nicht für Wettkämpfe gedacht ist und nur der Entspannung dient.", "Weil es nur langsame Bewegungen ohne echte Techniken enthält."], answer: "Weil es Schlagtechniken, Tritte, Würfe und Bodenkampf in einem System vereint." },
      { question: "20. In welcher Position beginnt ein Kampf in SUDO?", options: ["Dur", "Hazir", "Hazir-ol", "Atli"], answer: "Hazir-ol" },
      { question: "21. Welche Schläge sind in SUDO verboten (nennen Sie die drei wichtigsten)?", options: ["Faustschläge ins Gesicht, Schläge auf den Hinterkopf, Schläge auf die Genitalien.", "Handflächenschläge auf den Bauch, leichte Tritte gegen das Bein, Ohrfeigen.", "Leichtes Antippen mit dem Fuß, Schulterhiebe, Kniestoß gegen Oberschenkel."], answer: "Faustschläge ins Gesicht, Schläge auf den Hinterkopf, Schläge auf die Genitalien." },
      { question: "22. Welche Haltung gilt in SUDO als die effektivste?", options: ["Otur", "Rahat-otur", "Rahat", "Hazir-ol"], answer: "Hazir-ol" },
      { question: "23. Welche Kombination ist in SUDO nicht effektiv?", options: ["Tritt zum Körper", "Dreimal mit der Faust auf die Schulter schlagen und dann rückwärts laufen", "Fußfeger", "Bodenkontrolle"], answer: "Dreimal mit der Faust auf die Schulter schlagen und dann rückwärts laufen" },
      { question: "24. Was bedeutet 'Bodenarbeit' in SUDO?", options: ["Liegestütze als Aufwärmung", "Gegner nur berühren, um zu gewinnen", "Meditation ohne Kontakt", "Zweiter Kampfabschnitt im Kniestand mit Grifftechniken"], answer: "Zweiter Kampfabschnitt im Kniestand mit Grifftechniken" },
      { question: "25. Welche Aktion ist bei Würfen in SUDO verboten?", options: ["Gegner mit geradem Rücken werfen", "Gegner absichtlich auf den Kopf werfen", "Während des Wurfs atmen", "Wurf mit Kampfschrei begleiten"], answer: "Gegner absichtlich auf den Kopf werfen" },
      { question: "26. Welche Rolle spielt die Atmung während eines Kampfes im SUDO?", options: ["Unwichtig", "Nur durch den Mund atmen", "Atmung hilft, Ruhe und Kontrolle zu bewahren"], answer: "Atmung hilft, Ruhe und Kontrolle zu bewahren" },
      { question: "27. Wie wird der Gewinner eines SUDO-Kampfes ermittelt?", options: ["Durch Punkte, Aufgabe oder technischen Sieg", "Der mit dem lautesten Kampfschrei gewinnt", "Immer unentschieden"], answer: "Durch Punkte, Aufgabe oder technischen Sieg" },
      { question: "28. Was bedeutet der Begriff 'iki' in SUDO?", options: ["Bodenarbeit", "Aufgeben", "Punkt", "Kampfschrei"], answer: "Punkt" },
      { question: "29. Welche Arten von Verwarnungen gibt es in SUDO?", options: ["1 (Kobud)", "2 (Kobud, Jaza)", "3 (Kobud, Jaza, Chikh)", "4 (Kobud, Jaza, Chikh, Galkh)"], answer: "3 (Kobud, Jaza, Chikh)" },
      { question: "30. Welche Geste des Richters weist auf Disqualifikation hin?", options: ["Kobud", "Jaza", "Chikh", "Galkh"], answer: "Chikh" },
      { question: "31. Welche Handlung führt zur sofortigen Disqualifikation?", options: ["Absichtlicher Schlag mit der Faust auf den Kopf", "Zu leiser Kampfschrei", "Schweiß auf der Matte", "Absichtlicher Kopftreffer"], answer: "Absichtlicher Schlag mit der Faust auf den Kopf" },
      { question: "32. Welche Regel gilt nicht für die Ausrüstung von Sportlern?", options: ["Oda ist Pflicht", "Sockenfarbe muss zum Gürtel passen", "Barfuß kämpfen", "Handschuhe in Runde 2 ausziehen"], answer: "Sockenfarbe muss zum Gürtel passen" },
      { question: "33. Wo fand die erste offizielle SUDO-Weltmeisterschaft statt?", options: ["Istanbul-2012", "Vagos-2012", "Baku-2012", "Paderborn-2012"], answer: "Baku-2012" },
      { question: "34. Welche Länder führen bei den SUDO-Grandchampions?", options: ["Lettland", "Guinea-Bissau", "Aserbaidschan", "Kanada", "Deutschland", "Senegal"], answer: "Lettland" },
      { question: "35. Was bedeutet der Ausdruck 'Sei wie Wasser' in der SUDO-Philosophie?", options: ["Wasser ist stärker als Feuer, vermeide Hitze", "Anpassungsfähig, fließend und stark", "Nur bei Regen kämpfen"], answer: "Anpassungsfähig, fließend und stark" },
      { question: "36. Was bedeutet 'Otur' in SUDO?", options: ["Aufstehen", "Bereit zum Kampf", "Hinsetzen", "Kampfhaltung"], answer: "Hinsetzen" },
      { question: "37. Was ist die höchste Punktzahl im Wettbewerb?", options: ["Uch", "Galaba", "Bir", "Iki"], answer: "Galaba" },
      { question: "38. Schüler-Lehrer-Rangordnung in SUDO", options: ["Bash Ustad, Namized, Ustad, Shagird, Muellim, Bash Muellim", "Namized, Ustad, Shagird, Muellim, Bash Muellim, Bash Ustad", "Namized, Shagird, Muellim, Bash Muellim, Ustad, Bash Ustad", "Shagird, Namized, Muellim, Bash Muellim, Ustad, Bash Ustad"], answer: "Shagird, Namized, Muellim, Bash Muellim, Ustad, Bash Ustad" },
      { question: "39. Welche ist 2025 die größte SUDO-Schule der Welt?", options: ["WSA Paderborn", "Baku Sudo Academy", "SUDO GmbH", "SUDO India"], answer: "WSA Paderborn" },
      { question: "40. Was ist das größte Ziel von SUDO?", options: ["Nächste Weltmeisterschaft austragen", "Teilnahme an den Olympischen Spielen", "Eigenes Weltzentrum eröffnen", "Maximale Studierendenzahl im WSF Institut erreichen"], answer: "Teilnahme an den Olympischen Spielen" }
    ],
    ru: [
      { question: "1. Сколько раундов в поединке по СУДО?", options: ["1", "2", "3", "4"], answer: "3" },
      { question: "2. Как называется одежда бойца СУДО?", options: ["Кимоно", "Одежда судо", "Ги", "Ода"], answer: "Ода" },
      { question: "3. Что означает СУДО в переводе?", options: ["Стиль боя, основанный на жёстких ударах и статических позициях", "Бой, подобный свойствам воды", "Древняя философия боевых искусств из Греции"], answer: "Бой, подобный свойствам воды" },
      { question: "4. Кто является основателем СУДО?", options: ["Брюс Ли", "Чак Норрис", "Сабир Сулейман", "Дзигоро Кано"], answer: "Сабир Сулейман" },
      { question: "5. В каком году было основано СУДО?", options: ["1877", "1977", "2014", "2011"], answer: "2011" },
      { question: "6. В какой стране было основано СУДО?", options: ["Азербайджан", "Германия", "Япония", "США"], answer: "Азербайджан" },
      { question: "7. Где находится штаб-квартира СУДО?", options: ["Дубай", "Падерборн", "Баку", "Нью-Йорк"], answer: "Падерборн" },
      { question: "8. Кто является почётным президентом Всемирной федерации СУДО?", options: ["Нарухито", "Барак Хусейн Обама II", "Чак Норрис"], answer: "Чак Норрис" },
      { question: "9. Кто является президентом Всемирной федерации СУДО?", options: ["Сабир Сулейман", "Антонио Багуэрас", "Грандмастер Рахим", "Гэри Стив"], answer: "Сабир Сулейман" },
      { question: "10. Какова основная философия СУДО?", options: ["Воздух", "Камень", "Вода", "Человек"], answer: "Вода" },
      { question: "11. Как звучит приветствие в СУДО?", options: ["Бонжур", "Са", "Ос", "Оссу"], answer: "Са" },
      { question: "12. Как называется место, где тренируются по СУДО?", options: ["Зал СУДО", "Додзе", "Тренировочный зал", "Оджаг"], answer: "Оджаг" },
      { question: "13. Перечислите все раунды на соревнованиях по СУДО по порядку.", options: ["Микс, Дойуш-Дошек, Дойуш, Дошек", "Дойуш, Дошек, Микс", "Дошек, Дойуш, Микс"], answer: "Дойуш, Дошек, Микс" },
      { question: "14. Какие цвета одежды у бойца СУДО?", options: ["Белый, Синий", "Белый, Синий, Красный", "Белый, Красный", "Красный, Синий"], answer: "Красный, Синий" },
      { question: "15. Какой чемпионат мира по СУДО прошёл в 2024 году в Падерборне?", options: ["8", "12", "13", "14"], answer: "13" },
      { question: "16. На скольких языках была издана книга 'Гений СУДО' в 2022 году?", options: ["1", "3", "5", "6"], answer: "6" },
      { question: "17. Какая организация официально представляет СУДО во всем мире?", options: ["World Sudo Federation", "World SUDO Center", "Paderborn Sudo Academy", "Westfalen SUDO Association"], answer: "World Sudo Federation" },
      { question: "18. Чем СУДО отличается от карате, дзюдо и тхэквондо?", options: ["СУДО более универсален, так как объединяет удары, пинки, броски и борьбу на полу.", "СУДО менее универсален, так как включает только простые удары и не допускает борьбу на полу.", "СУДО сосредоточен исключительно на медитации и не содержит боевых техник.", "По сравнению с тхэквондо СУДО сильно ограничен и не допускает пинков и бросков."], answer: "СУДО более универсален, так как объединяет удары, пинки, броски и борьбу на полу." },
      { question: "19. Почему СУДО называют универсальной боевой системой?", options: ["Потому что она объединяет удары, пинки, броски и борьбу в одной системе.", "Потому что основана только на дыхательных техниках и медитации.", "Потому что она не предназначена для соревнований и служит только для расслабления.", "Потому что состоит только из медленных движений без настоящих техник."], answer: "Потому что она объединяет удары, пинки, броски и борьбу в одной системе." },
      { question: "20. В какой позиции начинается бой в СУДО?", options: ["Дур", "Хазир", "Хазир-ол", "Атлы"], answer: "Хазир-ол" },
      { question: "21. Какие удары запрещены в СУДО (назовите 3 главных)?", options: ["Удары кулаком в лицо, по затылку и по гениталиям.", "Пощечины, лёгкие удары по животу, пинки по ноге.", "Прыжки без удара, удары по плечу, подножки."], answer: "Удары кулаком в лицо, по затылку и по гениталиям." },
      { question: "22. Какая стойка считается самой эффективной в СУДО?", options: ["Отур", "Рахат-отур", "Рахат", "Хазир-ол"], answer: "Хазир-ол" },
      { question: "23. Какая комбинация неэффективна в СУДО?", options: ["Удар по корпусу", "Три удара по плечу и отход назад", "Сваливание ногой", "Контроль в партере"], answer: "Три удара по плечу и отход назад" },
      { question: "24. Что означает 'работа в партере' в СУДО?", options: ["Отжимания для разминки", "Победа после касания соперника", "Медитация без контакта", "Второй раунд на коленях с приёмами захвата и контроля"], answer: "Второй раунд на коленях с приёмами захвата и контроля" },
      { question: "25. Какое действие запрещено при бросках в СУДО?", options: ["Бросок с прямой спиной", "Преднамеренный бросок на голову", "Дыхание во время броска", "Бросок с криком"], answer: "Преднамеренный бросок на голову" },
      { question: "26. Какова роль дыхания в поединке СУДО?", options: ["Не важно", "Только через рот", "Помогает сохранять спокойствие и контроль"], answer: "Помогает сохранять спокойствие и контроль" },
      { question: "27. Как определяется победитель поединка СУДО?", options: ["По очкам, сдаче соперника или технической победе", "По громкости боевого крика", "Всегда ничья"], answer: "По очкам, сдаче соперника или технической победе" },
      { question: "28. Что означает термин 'ики' в СУДО?", options: ["Работа в партере", "Сдача", "Очко", "Боевой крик"], answer: "Очко" },
      { question: "29. Какие предупреждения есть в СУДО?", options: ["1 (Кобуд)", "2 (Кобуд, Джаза)", "3 (Кобуд, Джаза, Чих)", "4 (Кобуд, Джаза, Чих, Гальх)"], answer: "3 (Кобуд, Джаза, Чих)" },
      { question: "30. Какой жест судьи указывает на дисквалификацию?", options: ["Кобуд", "Джаза", "Чих", "Гальх"], answer: "Чих" },
      { question: "31. Какие действия ведут к немедленной дисквалификации?", options: ["Умышленный удар кулаком в голову", "Слишком тихий крик", "Пот на татами", "Преднамеренный удар по голове"], answer: "Умышленный удар кулаком в голову" },
      { question: "32. Какое правило не относится к экипировке спортсменов?", options: ["Ода обязательна", "Цвет носков должен совпадать с поясом", "Бойцы дерутся босиком", "Перчатки снимаются во втором раунде"], answer: "Цвет носков должен совпадать с поясом" },
      { question: "33. Где прошёл первый официальный чемпионат мира по СУДО?", options: ["Стамбул-2012", "Вагос-2012", "Баку-2012", "Падерборн-2012"], answer: "Баку-2012" },
      { question: "34. Какие страны лидируют по количеству грандчемпионов СУДО?", options: ["Латвия", "Гвинея-Бисау", "Азербайджан", "Канада", "Германия", "Сенегал"], answer: "Латвия" },
      { question: "35. Что означает фраза 'Будь как вода' в философии СУДО?", options: ["Вода сильнее огня, избегай жара", "Гибкость, текучесть и сила — быть адаптивным", "Сражаться только под дождём"], answer: "Гибкость, текучесть и сила — быть адаптивным" },
      { question: "36. Что означает 'Отур' в СУДО?", options: ["Встать", "Готов к бою", "Сесть", "Боевая стойка"], answer: "Сесть" },
      { question: "37. Какой наивысший балл в соревнованиях?", options: ["Уч", "Галаба", "Бир", "Ики"], answer: "Галаба" },
      { question: "38. Ранжирование ученик-преподаватель в СУДО", options: ["Баш Устад, Намиэд, Устад, Шагирд, Муэллим, Баш Муэллим", "Намиэд, Устад, Шагирд, Муэллим, Баш Муэллим, Баш Устад", "Намиэд, Шагирд, Муэллим, Баш Муэллим, Устад, Баш Устад", "Шагирд, Намиэд, Муэллим, Баш Муэллим, Устад, Баш Устад"], answer: "Шагирд, Намиэд, Муэллим, Баш Муэллим, Устад, Баш Устад" },
      { question: "39. Какая школа СУДО самая большая в мире в 2025 году?", options: ["WSA Paderborn", "Баку СУДО Академия", "SUDO GmbH", "SUDO Индия"], answer: "WSA Paderborn" },
      { question: "40. Какова главная цель СУДО?", options: ["Проведение следующего чемпионата мира", "Участие в Олимпийских играх", "Открытие собственного мирового центра", "Максимальное количество студентов в институте WSF"], answer: "Участие в Олимпийских играх" }
    
    ]
  };
  
  export default quizContent;
  